INVENTORY TO THE PIERCE FAMILY PAPERS, 1841-1940 D-022
University of California, Davis General Library, Dept. of Special Collections
- George W. Pierce, Sr., 1841-1905.; Series 1.; 415 items, 1.5 linear ft.
  - Financial Records, n.d., incomplete date, 1841 - 1889; Subseries 1.3.; 275 items
    - Tax Records, (1841 - 1887); Subseries 1.3.1.; 61 items
      Tax records include income, poll, and property tax bills and receipts for the Pierce Family during the years 1841 - 1887. Assessment lists are also part of this sub-subseries.
      - Assessment Lists, 7 items
        - n.d., 1881-1889 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Tax Bills, 5 items
        - 1880-1885 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Tax Receipts, 49 items
        - Receipts, 1841-1851; 8 items (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Receipts, 1853-1869; 23 items (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - Receipts, 1871-1887; 18 items (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Account Statements, Promissory Notes, and Receipts; n.d., incomplete date, 1853-1889; Subseries 1.3.2.; 177 items
      These account statements, promissory notes, and receipts pertain to Pierce Family and Ranch purchases, payments, and income for the years 1853-1889. Materials are arranged chronologically and grouped in 10 folders with undated items in the first folder. Because the senior Pierce gave up control of the ranch to his son on September 18,1888, most Pierce Family and Ranch financial records after that date are part of the George W. Pierce, Jr. series.
      - n.d. or incomplete date, 13 items (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - 1853-1859, 6 items. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 1860-1863, 24 items (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - 1866-1868, 13 items (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - 1870-1876, 15 items (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - 1877-1879, 31 items (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - 1880-1883, 29 items (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - 1884-1885, 17 items (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - 1886-1887, 20 items (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - 1888-1889, 9 items (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Account Books, 1845-1882; Subseries 1.3.3.; 37 items
      Account books are the third type of financial records in the George W. Pierce, Sr. Series. These 4 account books (1845-1882) include financial records from Pierce's old home in Southport, WI and records for the Pierce Ranch and Family in Davisville, CA. One account book was also used as a scrapbook and contains many clippings from the 1860s.
      - Accounts begun in Southport, WI / Kenosha, WI and continued in Yolo County, CA, 1 volume with inserts of 3 notes and 1 telegram, 1845-1869; 5 items (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Accounts for Pierce Family Ranch and Office of Justice of the Peace, Yolo County, CA, 1 volume, 1856-1861; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Time book for laborers on Pierce Family Ranch, 1 volume, 1868-1882; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Accounts for Pierce Family Ranch and records for Justice of the Peace, Yolo County, CA, Account book converted into scrapbook, 1 volume, circa 1860-1869; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Clippings from account book/scrapbook, circa, 1860-1869; 29 items (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Diaries, 1852-1890; Subseries 1.4.; 27 items (20 volumes and 7 leaves)
    Diaries, the fourth subseries of Series I, consists of 20 diaries (and 7 loose leaves) written by George W. Pierce, Sr. during the years 1852-1890. The diaries are arranged chronologically, and diaries for some years are missing. Pierce's diaries provide researchers with financial information as well as commentary about ranch and family events. Pierce's 1888 diary was written in an 1884 diary book. On Sept. 17, 1888, entries in the 1888 diary begin to be made by Pierce's son, George W. Pierce, Jr. An 1889 diary book was converted into the 1890 diary. Eunice Pierce wrote the final entries for her husband's 1890 diary--detailing the last 11 days of the life of the senior George W. Pierce--on an inserted leaf of paper.
    - Travel Journal with short account of move from Kenosha, WI / Southport, WI to California and a list of expenses, 1 volume, 1852; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Diary, 1 volume, 1867; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1870; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Diary, 1 volume, 1871; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Diary, Accounts, and Draft of remarks made to Independent Order of Odd Fellows, Yolo Lodge no. 169, 1 volume, 1 leaf, 1872-1873; 2 items (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Diary, 1 volume, 1873; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1874; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Diary, 1 volume, 1 leaf, 1877-[1878]; 2 items (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1 leaf, 1879; 2 items (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Dairy and Accounts, 1 volume, 1 leaf, 1880-1881; 2 items (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1881; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1882; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1883; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1884; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Diary and note, 1 volume, 1 leaf, 1885; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1886; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1887; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Diary, 1 volume and 1 leaf., 1888; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1889; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Diary, 1 volume, 1 leaf, 1890; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Printed Material, 1863-1879; Subseries 1.5.; 16 items
    The last subseries of Series I is Printed Material. Printed Material is divided into items having to do with organizations or other subjects.
    - Organizations, 1863-1879; Subseries 1.5.1.; 10 items
      - California Wine Growers Association
        - Certificate of membership, 1867; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Freemasons
        - Pamphlet; "By-Laws of Woodland Lodge No. 156 of Free and Accepted Masons," San Francisco, CA: Franklin Printing House, 1872; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Independent Order of Odd Fellows, 1863-1879; 7 items
        - Anniversary Hymns, incomplete date, 1 item (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - Newspaper, "New Age,", Sept. 30, 1871; 1 item (Box 10, Folder 4)
        - Pamphlets, 1863-1879; 3 items
          - Pamphlet: "Constitution and by-laws of Woodland Lodge No. 111, I.O.O.F.," Sacramento, CA: Crocker, H. S., 1871; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Pamphlet: "Constitution, by-laws and rules of order of Woodland Lodge No. 111, I.O. of O.F.," Sacramento, CA: Crocker, H. S., 1863; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 13)
          - Pamphlet: "Proceedings of the twenty-seventh annual communication of the R. W. Grand Lodge of the State of California,", 1879; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - "Responses to be used at the dedication of the Odd Fellows Hall at Suisun,", April 25, 1873; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Patrons of Husbandry - National Grange
        - Pamphlet; "Constitution of the order of Patrons of Husbandry and by-laws of the National Grange," Washington, D.C.: Gibson Brothers, 1873; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Other Printed Material, 1867-1879; Subseries 1.5.2.; 6 items
      - Broadside, Administrator's sale for the estate of S. J. Thomas, 1867; 1 item (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Hymn, 1877; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Newspapers; "The Daily Republican;" Woodland, CA, Aug. 21, 1879; Aug. 29, 1879; Sept. 1, 1879; Sept. 2, 1879; 4 items (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Eunice Pierce, 1867-1908; Series 2.; 68 items, .5 linear feet
  Series II (1867-1908) is composed of items created by or collected by Eunice Pierce. This series is divided into 5 subseries: Correspondence, Legal Documents, Financial Records, Diaries, and Printed Material.
  - Correspondence, 1879-1895; Subseries 2.1.; 11 items
    The subseries, Correspondence, is mainly related to property held by Eunice Pierce. It is divided into outgoing and incoming correspondence and then listed in alphabetical order by the name of the correspondent.
    - Outgoing, 1888; Subseries 2.1.1.; 1 item
      - McDougall, J. H., letter, Dec. 20, 1888; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Incoming, 1879-1890; Subseries 2.1.2.; 10 items
      - Briggs, H. W., letter and 2 envelopes, 1893-1895; 3 items (Box 2, Folder 20.1)
      - Davies, Work, McNamee and Hilton, Law Offices, 2 letters, 1879-1882; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 20.2)
      - Evalyn [sister], letter and envelope, Oct. 29, 1892; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 20.3)
      - Frost, C. S., letter and envelope, Sept. 16, 1892; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 20.4)
      - Sacramento Bank; Coleman, William P., President, letter, May 12, 1890; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 20.5)
  - Legal Documents, 1897-1906; Subseries 2.2.; 3 items
    The subseries, Legal Documents, consists of an abstract of title (including deeds and tax receipts) for a Yolo County, CA property and insurance policies for property.
    - Abstract of Title, 1897-1906; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Insurance policies for property, 1904-1907; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Financial Records, 1867-1904; Subseries 2.3.; 38 items
    Tax receipts along with account statements, promissory notes, and receipts make up the Financial Records subseries.
    - Tax Receipts, 1874-1904; 20 items
      These tax receipts are records of Eunice Pierce's payment of property and school taxes for Woodland, CA, Yolo County, CA, and Monterey County, CA. Many of the receipts describe property owned by the Pierce Family.
      - Tax receipts, 1874-1888; 12 items (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Tax receipts, 1889-1904; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Account Statements, Promissory Notes, and Receipts
      - n.d., 1867-1905, 18 items (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Diaries, 1891-1900; Subseries 2.4.; 13 items
    The diaries are arranged chronologically.
    - Diary entries on 2 leaves of paper, Jan. 2, [1891] - Jan. 24, [1891]; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1891; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1892; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1 card, 1895; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1896; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1897; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Diary, Accounts, List, and Receipt; 1 volume and 2 leaves, 1898; 3 items (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1899; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Diary and Accounts, 1 volume, 1900; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Printed Material, 1908; Subseries 2.5.
    - Funeral notices for Eunice Pierce,., Oct. 26, 1908; 3 items (Box 2, Folder 35)
- George W. Pierce, Jr., 1864-1931; Series 3.; 1328 Linear Feet
  Series III. (1864-1931) is the largest series (1328 items or 6 linear feet) and makes up the bulk of the Pierce Family Papers. Series III is comprised of items created or collected by George W. Pierce, Jr. and is divided into seven subseries: Correspondence; Legal Documents; Financial Records; Diaries, Notes, and Meeting Minutes; Creative Works; Printed Material; and Artifacts.
  - Correspondence, n.d., 1876-1931; Subseries 3.1.; 398 items
    The Correspondence subseries is divided into outgoing, incoming, and collected letters. Within these three designations, items are listed in alphabetical order by the correspondents' last names or by the names of the organizations that they represent. Therefore, a researcher in search of a certain letter should look for the letter under both the names of possible correspondents and the names of their organizations. Notable correspondents include California Governors Hiram W. Johnson and George C. Pardee; Lieutenant-Governor Alden Anderson; Senator U. S. Webb; and University of California key players James Forsyth Hunt, V. H. Henderson, Benjamin Ide Wheeler, and E. J. Wickson. In addition to letters, the correspondence subseries also includes materials such as envelopes, lists, statements, postcards, telegrams, brochures, fliers, railroad passes, invitations, forms, and other enclosures. If it was possible to identify which items (including copies of other authors' letters) were enclosed with letters, these enclosures have been kept with the letters with which they were sent.
    - Outgoing, n.d., 1901-1913; Subseries 3.1.1.; 78 items
      Researchers can gain insight into the personality and many activities of George W. Pierce, Jr. through these carbon copies of outgoing letters he wrote on subjects such as promotion of Yolo County, CA and Davisville, CA; agricultural technology; complaints about products or services (for example, automobiles); Pierce's various business ventures including Sacramento Valley Electric Railroad Company, California Almond Growers' Exchange, and California Grain Growers' Association; and his campaign to encourage the State Farm Commission and the University of California to choose Davisville, CA (Davis, CA) as the site for the University Farm. Letters to Governor George C. Pardee, U. S. Webb, and other members of the State Farm Commission discuss the selection of Davisville, CA as the future site for the University Farm.
      - Balfour, Douglas, 1 cc. letter, Feb. 22, 1904; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 36.1)
      - Best Manufacturing Company, 4 cc. letters, 1910-1911; 4 items (Box 2, Folder 36.2)
      - Brittain, John A., 1 cc. letter, July 23, 1907; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 36.3)
      - California Promotion Committee, 1 cc. letter, March 25, 1907; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 36.4)
      - Davis, William R., 1 cc. letter, June 27, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 36.5)
      - Dawson, W. T., 1 cc. letter, June 15, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 36.6)
      - Donohoe, Charles L., 2 cc. letters, 1913; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 36.7)
      - Electric Appliance Company, 2 cc. letters, 1913; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 36.8)
      - Fancher Creek Nurseries, 1 cc. list, Dec. 26, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 37.1)
      - Fischer, C. F., 1 cc. letter, June 28, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 37.2)
      - Gillett, James N., Governor of California, 1 cc. letter, May 18, 1907; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 37.3)
      - Green, W. S., cc. letter, Nov. 27, 1904; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 37.4)
      - Hunt, James Forsyth, cc. letter, Feb. 5, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 38.1)
      - Jeffrey, Thomas B. and Company, cc. letter, Aug. 2, 1907; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 38.2)
      - Jefferies, Thomas G. and Company, cc. letter, Aug. 4, 1907; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 38.3)
      - Johnson, Hiram W., Governor of California, cc. letter, March 15, 1911; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 38.4)
      - Johnson, J. D. and Son, cc. letter, July 7, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 38.5)
      - Kent, W. H. and George C. Perkins, 2 cc. letters and 2 handwritten drafts on 2 leaves, Feb. 8, 1913; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 38.6)
      - Knox Automobile Company, 2 cc. letters, Sept. 19, 1904; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 38.7)
      - Leavitt and Bill, cc. letter, Sept. 14, 1904; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 38.8)
      - Lehe, Edward N., cc. letter, June 15, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 38.9)
      - Lukens, G. R., cc. letter, Aug. 20, 1902; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 38.10)
      - McSweeney, Ambrose, cc. letter, June 23, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.1)
      - Millican, Kenneth A., cc. letter, Dec. 9, 1907; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.2)
      - Morrison, W. L., cc. letter fragment, Sept. 21, 1904; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.3)
      - O'Gara, James J., cc. letter, Feb. 18, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.4)
      - O'Hara, Mrs. James, cc. letter, June 15, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.5)
      - Pacific Manufacturing Company, 2 cc. letters, 1913; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 39.6)
      - Pardee, George C., Governor of California, 6 cc. letters (1 with notes on reverse) and 1 handwritten letter draft with notes on reverse, 1904-1913; 7 items (Box 2, Folder 39.7)
      - Perkins, George C., cc. letter, Feb. 8, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.8)
      - Pfaff, M. G., cc. letter, April 14, 1907; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.9)
      - Reed, H. B., cc. letter, March 3, 1906; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.10)
      - Reith, John, Jr., cc. letter, March 29, 1905; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.11)
      - Rose, Charles T., 4 cc. letters, 1913; 4 items (Box 2, Folder 39.12)
      - Rule, F. K., cc. letter, Sept. 16, 1904; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 39.13)
      - Sheldon, M. N., cc. letter, June 18, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 40.1)
      - Southern Pacific Company; Brennan, J. D., Superintendent Western Division;; 2 cc. letters, 1913; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 40.2)
      - Stabler, H. P., cc. letter and statement, Nov. 27, 1904; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 40.3)
      - State Farm Commission; Henderson, V. H., Secretary;; 3 cc. letters, 1905-1906; 3 items (Box 2, Folder 40.4)
      - State Farm Commission, Members of, 5 cc. letters, 1 letter fragment, 1905-1906; 6 items (Box 2, Folder 40.5)
      - Talley Specialty Company, cc. letter, Jan. 22, 1904; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 41.1)
      - University of California Club, cc. letter, Aug. 5, 1905; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 41.2)
      - Webb, U. S., 3 cc. letters, 1906; 3 items (Box 2, Folder 41.3)
      - Wheeler, Benjamin Ide, President, University of California, 2 cc. letters, 1904-1905; 2 items (Box 2, Folder 41.4)
      - Wickson, E. J., cc. letter, Jan. 16, 1906; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 41.5)
      - Wilson, Rufus Rockwell, cc. letter, June 28, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 41.6)
      - Unidentified Recipient; Dear Sirs (concerning California Grain Growers' Association;; letter, Dec. 12, 1901; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 42.1)
      - Unidentified Recipient: Frankie (concerning Pierce Family activities), cc. letter, July 5, 1913; 1 item (Box 2, Folder 42.2)
      - Unidentified Recipient: To Whom it May Concern (concerning Davis, CA Postmaster), n.d., letter draft, 1 item (Box 2, Folder 42.3)
    - Incoming, 1876-1931; Subseries 3.1.2.; 322 items
      Incoming letters (1876-1931, 322 items) to George W. Pierce, Jr. are arranged in alphabetical order by the last names of the letters' authors or by the names of organizations from which the letters originated. Many of the letters dating (1905-1906) deal with the selection of Davis, CA as the site for the State University Farm. Authors of letters pertaining to the University Farm include: Alden Anderson, P. N. Ashley, W. E. Bates, J. H. Braly, Morris Brooke, John E. Budd, George C. Pardee, U. S. Webb, Benjamin Ide Wheeler, E. J. Wickson, members of the State Farm Commission, and Alfred Holman, Editor and Publisher of the Sacramento Union. Other letters have to do with Pierce's business ventures and farmers' marketing organizations: Silica Brick Company (correspondence from W. A. Beard, T. L. Myers, and Pacific Gas and Electric Company), Sacramento Valley Electric Railroad Company (J. E. Scarlett, H. G. Brown, Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company, B. F. Newby, and Marsh Brothers and Gardenier Incorporated), California Almond Growers' Exchange (under the name of the organization and also under the names of their auditors Janes-Frase Company, and of Albert E. Boynton), California Grain Growers' Association (D. B. Groff, and A. Bannister), and Putah Creek Water Company (J. C. Pierson). Pierce received numerous letters (1901-1908) from prominent Davisville, CA landowner and business man, M. Diggs. These letters concern the sale of land near Davisville, CA. Some of Pierce's other interests such as farm labor, the promotion of Yolo County, CA and water rights are also demonstrated by the letters he received. Of special interest to those researching farm labor is a letter written by Mousha Singh, a Sikh and Pierce's long-time and most valued ranch hand. Singh was Pierce's link to securing other Sikh laborers during harvest time.
      - Anderson, Alden, Lieutenant-Governor of California, 4 letters, 4 envelopes, 1906; 8 items (Box 3, Folder 1.1)
      - Ashley, P. N., 2 copies of 1 letter, June 7, 1906; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 1.2)
      - Athens Lodge, No. 228, [Freemasons], Davisville, CA, invitation, ticket, and envelope, Oct. 4, 1876; 3 items (Box 3, Folder 1.3)
      - Bank of Yolo; C. W. Bush, President;; form letter, Aug. 5, 1912; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 1.4)
      - Bannister, A., letter and envelope, Aug. 20, 1902; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 2.1)
      - Bates, W. E., letter, 1906; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 2.2)
      - Beard, W. A., 2 letters, envelope, and copy of letter from E. W. Hilgard, 1911; 4 items (Box 3, Folder 2.3)
      - Boynton, Albert E., letter, May 21, 1918; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 2.4)
      - Braly, J. H., letter and envelope, March 31, 1905; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 2.5)
      - Brooke, Morris, letter, Feb. 14, 1906; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 2.6)
      - Brown, H. G., letter, Aug. 16, 1918; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 2.7)
      - Budd, John E., 5 letters and 2 envelopes, 1906; 7 items (Box 3, Folder 2.8)
      - California Almond Growers' Exchange, 1 postcard, 2 copies of letters from Dudley, U. H. and Company, 1919-1920; 3 items (Box 3, Folder 3.1)
      - California Almond Growers' Exchange; J. P. Dargitz, Secretary and Manager;; letter with statement, 1910; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 3.2)
      - California Almond Growers' Exchange; T. C. Tucker, Manager;; 6 letters, 1 statement, 4 envelopes, 1912-1922; 11 items (Box 3, Folder 3.3)
      - California Almond Growers' Exchange; B. F. Walton; President;; letter, Aug. 9, 1912; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 3.4)
      - California. State Commission of Horticulture; G. H. Hecke; State Commissioner of Horticulture;; letter and envelope, Oct. 29, 1918; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 4.1)
      - California. State Committee on Efficiency and Economy; Albert E. Boyton, Chairman;; letter, list, and envelope, Jan. 21, 1919; 3 items (Box 3, Folder 4.2)
      - California State Prison, San Quentin, CA, Jute Mill Department; John C. Edgar, Warden;; letter, legal doc., and envelope, Jan. 31, 1907; 3 items (Box 3, Folder 4.3)
      - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Company; N. E. Otterson, District Manager;; letter, envelope, and 2 fliers, Dec. 18, 1914; 4 items (Box 3, Folder 4.4)
      - Cook, Thomas and Son, World Wide Travel Service, letter and brochure, March 9, 1926; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 4.5)
      - Crandall, F. W., postcard, Feb. 21, 1903; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 4.6)
      - Dargitz, J. P., letter and envelope, Dec. 24, 1918; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 5.1)
      - Davis Business Men's Association, Davis, CA; H. B. Crego, Secretary;; letter, May 11, 1922; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 5.2)
      - DeLaval Dairy Supply Company; Charles A. Crate, Sales Department;; 1 letter and 1 copy of letter from Newman Brothers of Poppy Ridge Ranch, Elk Grove, CA, 1914; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 5.3)
      - Diggs, M., 14 letters and 14 envelopes, 1901-1908; 28 items (Box 3, Folder 6.1)
      - Dixon Chamber of Commerce, Dixon, CA; R. Moss, Publicity Committee;; letter, April 1, 1913; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 6.2)
      - Fancher Creek Nurseries, 1914-1915; 5 items (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Franklin Paint Company;; 3 form letters, 6 envelopes, 2 roofing samples, 3 brochures, and 6 order forms, 1926; 20 items (Box 3, Folder 8.1)
      - French, F. W., letter, Feb. 6, 1903; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 8.2)
      - Fulton Paint Company;; 1 form letter, 2 envelopes, 2 roofing samples, 1 brochure, and 2 order forms, 1926; 8 items (Box 3, Folder 8.3)
      - Gregory, W. H., 2 letters, Sept. 10, 1906; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 9.1)
      - Griffith Brokerage Company, n.d., 4 fliers, 1919; 4 items (Box 3, Folder 9.2)
      - Groff, D. B., (regarding California Grain Growers' Association), letter, Dec. 17, 1901; 1 item (Box 3, Folder 9.3)
      - Hecke, G. H., letter and envelope, Sept. 15, 1915; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 10.1)
      - Hendy, Joshua, Machine Works;; letter, flier, and envelope, Feb. 20, 1884; 3 items (Box 3, Folder 10.2)
      - Howell-Dohrmann Company; George W. Howell;; letter and envelope, May 29, 1912; 2 items (Box 3, Folder 10.3)
      - Janes-Frase Company, Auditors and Public Accountants; Louis L. Janes, Manager Commercial Department;; 16 letters with accounts for the California Almond Growers' Exchange, 1923; 16 items (Box 3, Folder 11.1)